We have arrived! We have arrived!
Keep working hard!
Please, I can't take this anymore!
What are you talking about?
If you can't even handle this, you're guaranteed to be devoured.
Hey, it's Tokito!
Hey, you! If this were a real fight, you'd be dead three times over.
It's over.
If it wasn't looked at the reason,
It's true that it's the absolute future
It doesn't think uncomfortable with
flesh.
Don't leak things that are
How to fight to find challenges again,
or how to locate the universe.
I just embrace the circumstances,
that's between you and you.
I show you how we will Always change you.
Subscribe to get more information.
Bye!
and keep Projektion
Let's go!
Even if you're hit, you have to move, and pull yourself together.
Try your best to follow my movements.
Oh look, you've died again.
Listen, even if someone falls, never stop moving.
The second you do that is the second you die.
Hey, Tanjiro, it's been a while.
I see you're recovered.
You're about as useless as they come.
You're better off getting devoured by a demon!
Hey, wait, I remember you!
What do you think you're looking at, bottom feeder?
Tokito's Kasugai Crow is here too.
And she's still as cruel as ever.
Loud mouth.
Leave us alone.
Huh?
You shut your mouth, or I'll get out both your eyes!
Oh, hey Tokito.
It's good to see you.
I can hardly wait to start our training.
I'm excited myself, Tanjiro.
I want to show you something.
Use that water sparingly, you slackers!
Do you ever stop talking?
What?
We're coming in.
Oh, hello, Lord Tokito.
Mr. Kanamori!
Hmm?
Well, if it isn't young Tanjiro in the flesh!
And it looks like you've healed up quite nicely!
Thank goodness!
Yes, thank you very much.
So why are you here?
Because I invited him here.
Tanjiro, would you mind holding this?
Step back a little and hold it with the blade facing me.
Like this?
That's it. Now hold still.
What do you think?
It's so sharp!
Now you see why I wanted Mr. Kanamori here.
Does that mean Mr. Kanamori is…
Sure does!
I've been stationed here to tend to all of his swords.
After what happened,
I want my swords to always be sharpened and ready for battle.
When I told the master,
he approved my request to have Mr. Kanamori stationed here.
The master approved that?
That's right.
He even built this room for Mr. Kanamori to use.
Though I'm thankful for what he's done,
I wish he would focus on recovering.
No matter the circumstance,
we're always first in his thoughts.
And we should be grateful for that, right?
You're wide open. Pick up your sword.
If you let your emotions guide your attacks,
you'll never be a match for your opponent.
In all seriousness, you'd be a moth flying into a flame.
There are no do-overs when you're fighting a demon.
Even if you've only made one mistake,
one slip-up can be fatal.
You need to hone all of your movements.
Only then will you have a chance at surviving.
Let's call it a day then, shall we?
Hey, are you okay?
Oh, that looked bad.
Hey, Commodele.
Can you do us a favor and ask the Hashira
to ease up a little on us with the drills?
Yeah, at this rate, he'll kill us before a demon does.
You know,
I bet this training is harder on Tokito than it is on us.
I mean, after all,
he's been training us non-stop by himself.
You have a point.
Right?
Here, use this.
Thank you.
It'd be nice if he could at least drop that tone he has with us.
It is pretty soul-crushing, isn't it?
Uh-huh.
You say that, but to me it seems like he's toned it down a bit
compared to how he was before.
Seriously?
Then it's hopeless.
Isn't that Tokito?
I wonder where he's going.
He goes somewhere every day like this before nightfall.
He's probably having dinner if I had to guess.
Look at him.
I'm not smell to theели of odd himself
So I'm for it...
OK, so he's not
a little ál'm.
có lửa
That goes down
I'm not gonna miss her
Wind Breathing
Fourth Form
Rising Dust Storm
Serpent Breathing
Fifth Form
Slithering Serpent
Guess we're even
Seems like it, doesn't it?
I'd like to join in on the fun too
Tokito, huh?
You come all this way out here to spar with us every day
Isn't this affecting your daytime training?
While it might be sufficient training for the other Corps members
It's not quite enough to satisfy me
Well, yeah
That's why we come out here
Because this is the real Hashira training for us
Yeah, but it's not fair to keep this just to yourselves
Anyway, out of respect for your efforts, Tokito
Shinazugawa and I decided we'll be taking you on two against one
Let's go
Two against one, huh?
That's no fair
If you say so
Ready?
Start!
Nice work!
They can hardly keep up with you
Show them how a real Hashira fight
Shut up!
Today's training hit hard again
If we'd lost our focus for even a second
Someone could have gotten hurt
Well, I would hope so
Otherwise, there'd be no point in training
Taking on the Corps members by day
Then training alongside two other Hashira by night
Not bad at all
Tokito
How's your daytime training been treating you?
Well
Tanjiro came today
He's alive
I thought for sure he would be dead by now
Looks like his wounds are healing nicely
He'll most likely be fully recovered by the time he gets to your place, Mr. Igaro
Is that so?
Good
That means I can be thorough when I'm training him
Just because he got somewhat stronger
Doesn't mean he's anywhere near a match for a Hashira
We'll show him
That sounds really fun
Good luck, Tanjiro
That's it
You're dead
You there
Never stop moving
See?
Now you're dead too
You know what it is
There's not enough urgency here
I have an idea
Why don't we try training with real swords?
Bring us some real swords
R-right!
Now
Let's begin
Wait, seriously?
Of course
I...
I can't
Come
All things considered, you didn't attack blindly. I'd say this is growth.
You don't have to say it. I already know that.
Compared to you, I have no idea how grueling battles can be.
I also know that every night you go off somewhere,
and when you return, your body's covered in bruises.
I've seen you cooling them off with water early in the morning.
We're going to work hard to get better, so…
I think you're all doing as well as you can,
but even so, that doesn't mean you can win.
The truth of the matter is, I don't want you all to get killed by a demon.
If possible, I want your lives to be long.
That is how I truly feel.
He's amazing!
Look at that! You've gotten even faster than before, Tanjiro!
You've got to make the switch from relaxing to tensing up your muscles more fluid.
That's good!
There you go!
Fight like that, and your stamina will last longer.
Now that your legs and lower back are in sync, I'd say you're ready.
It's time you move on to the next Hashira. Good work!
What? Seriously?
That's right.
But it's only been five days!
Yeah, but even so, you've mastered everything I taught you.
Really?
So, can we go with him too?
We have been here for two weeks now.
Did I say you could leave? You're all nowhere near ready.
Now, if you've done dry swings, you are to go practice striking until the dummy breaks.
Can you believe the difference?
Oh!
Hey, Tokito!
We should have a paper airplane tossing contest.
That's a bit random.
Ta-da!
Well, I heard that you're super into paper airplanes, Tokito.
And since it's something that's within my reach...
What kind of hobbies does Lord Tokito have?
Well, let's see.
Oh, there is one thing that comes to mind.
He likes paper airplanes a good bit.
Paper airplanes, huh?
Yup! Just look at all the ones that he made!
Whoa!
But if I win the challenge, you have to promise me that you'll speak more gently to the core members.
So, what do you say?
Huh.
Sure. Sounds good.
I'm not losing!
Well, you're not about to beat me.
You really are a good guy, you know that?
You're positive? If my plane flies longer once out of ten rounds, then I win the entire thing?
Yeah. It's only fair since you won't be able to beat me.
I can at least win one of the ten.
There's only one way to find out.
Ready when you are.
All right. When I give the signal, please toss them at the same time.
One, two, three, go!
This round's winner is Lord Tokito.
You got this, Kamado!
Yeah, you'll get him next time!
Go!
This round's winner is Lord Tokito.
No!
There's just one more round!
Give it all you've got, Tanjiro!
Right. I do only have to win once after all.
I lost.
There was no way I'd lose.
I said that, right?
Yeah, but I still thought that I could beat you at least once!
Hashira!
Would it be alright if I challenged you?
I'm good with paper airplanes.
Me too!
I once beat everyone in my village!
Hey!
I came in first at my village's paper airplane contest!
You want some?
I want to try!
Let's get some paper!
Would you mind letting me take a closer look at it?
This time for sure!
I can't burn rain!
Oh, shut up, Bottom Feeder!
What? You shut up!
I told you to shut up first!
You guys ready or what?
Yeah!
Ready...
And...
Oh!
I saw you in a
Ah!
I saw you in...
We'll be right back.
Because she conquered the sun, I believe Muzan Kibutsuji is coming after Nezuko.
It only makes sense.
After all, we've hardly seen any demons lately.
It's their absence that's allowed this Hashira training to take place.
I was worried sick about being away from Nezuko.
But if she came with me, I would be playing right into Muzan's hands.
It's too risky.
Not only would all the demons seeking Nezuko gather in force,
but Kibutsuji might have ended up going into hiding.
I'm going to keep training, get stronger than I am now, and then go get Nezuko.
I like how you're always so positive, Tanjiro.
I can't afford to be, because the person protecting Nezuko is someone I trust deeply.
Tanjiro.
Together, we'll defeat him.
Muzan Kibutsuji.
Let's mournn söyle.
2, 399
zostaH frustrating
Let's go
Oh
Ooh
That's
It's
The
Thank you.
It's my favorite!
If you spread the honey on a slice of bread, it's super-duper yummy!
It's even better if you mix in some butter!
At 3 o'clock, I'm going to brew some black tea, and then I'll make you some pancakes!
Sound good?
B-butter? Pancakes?
I barely know what black tea is!
We'll have sweets, bread, and pancakes!
Today, we're going to talk a bit about Tokito.
I have a feeling that there are still some things that I've forgotten, so I can't wait.
Alright, here's a Taisho-era secret.
Since before he joined the Corps, he says that he was so tough he could sleep through a thunderstorm and even a lightning strike.
But that makes me sound like I'm an insensitive guy.
And apparently nothing ever made him lose his appetite.
But knowing that I acted like my older brother, while my memory was still foggy, makes me think he was watching over me.
What a nice thought. Tokito.
Next, Episode 5, I Even Ate Demons!